Emmet Murray

October 28, 2017

Work Experience

Literatu - Automation and Web Development

August 2016 - Present

- Independently researching and developing solutions to problems involving large datasets of over 15,000 files
- Applied and developed skills in problem solving, aesthetic web design and programmatic automation.
- Working closely with co-workers to design an intuitive online service
- Major revamp of previous website
- Vastly reduced the time required by users to find the information they need

Volunteering

Code Club St Aloysius College - Tutor

March 2017 - Present

- Running an after-school programming club for differently aged and skilled students
- Creating lesson plans and tasks to introduce students to programming

The UNSW Tea & Coffee Society - Vice-President (previously President, Secretary)

October 2016 - Present

- Coordinating and organising weekly gatherings for a society with over 1000 members
- Led the logistics and organisation of a high tea outing for the society at QVB tea room, a successful event with over 100 guests

Education

University of New South Wales - Bachelor of Engineering, (Honours) Software

February 2016 - Present

- Distinction average
- UNSW Taido Club member
- Tea and Coffee Society member and vice-president
- $\bullet\,$ Computer Science Engineering Society Social Team

Etelä Tapiolan Lukio, Finland - Rotary Youth Exchange Student

January 2015 - January 2016

- Acquired conversational proficiency in Finnish in under a year of study
- Studied English literature, Spanish, German, mathematics, physics, Finnish and music in Finnish
- Adapted to a foreign environment by conquering language and cultural barriers
- Integrated into a fast-paced group-work situation with my peers.

Contact me

+61 431 890 818 e.minor.murray@gmail.com

Profile

I'm a dedicated and passionate student who enjoys solving challenging technical problems. My leadership abilities have been extended through my keen involvement in my work and volunteering experiences, which reflect my broad interests in the world. I have a calm disposition which allows me to work well in high stress environments.

Technical Skillset

C, Java, C++ program development

Web development (Javascript, Node.js, Flask, Apache)

Scripting (Perl, Python, UNIX Bash)

Version control (Git)

Familiar with UNIX based and Windows Operating systems

LATEX

Awards

Finnish National Certificate Of Language Proficiency

Surf Life Saving Australia Bronze Medallion

Macquarie Group & UNSW Software Engineering Prize